http://www.medicalcodingbooks.com/privacy

Medicalcodingbooks.com's Privacy Policy
Medicalcodingbooks.com values its customers and respects their privacy. We collect customer information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to help us better understand your needs and interests. Medicalcodingbooks.com recognizes that it must maintain and use customer information responsibly. We do not sell or rent the information you provide to third parties.
Credit card information is used only for payment processing and fraud prevention. Sensitive personal information is collected only to facilitate our financial service providers' credit decisions and will be shared with them only with your permission. Our financial services providers do not use credit card information and sensitive personal data for any other purpose. Medicalcodingbooks.com will not use your personal information for a different purpose other than stated when you provided your data.
Occasionally we may use your information to contact you for market research regarding Medicalcodingbooks.com products or services. From time to time, we may also send you emails to help us learn more about your shopping preferences. In addition, we may use information about your product interests and purchases to help us improve our site design and your shopping experience. If you make a purchase online or over the phone, we may also send you notices about our products, services, contests and promotions through postal mail. Non-personal data is aggregated and used to improve the customer experience, usability and site content.
MedicalCodingBooks.com would like to communicate with its Customers when we have new products or services we feel are of special interest to you. Unless you opt-out of communications from MedicalCodingBooks.com, you will receive the following types of communications:
Newsletters, Special Offers, and Product Updates.
We may send MedicalCodingBooks.com Customers a welcome e-mail, newsletter, or coupon to verify your participation in the MedicalCodingBooks.com products and services we offer. Established Customers will occasionally receive information on products, services and special deals or coupons.
Out of respect for the privacy of our Customers, we present the option to NOT receive these types of communications.
MedicalCodingBooks.com gives Customers the ability to opt-out of receiving future communications from MedicalCodingBooks.com by using the built-in "Unsubscribe" feature found in emailed communications. Customers can also send an email to customerservice@MedicalCodingBooks.com with "Unsubscribe" in the subject line to opt-out.
Customer Service.
MedicalCodingBooks.com communicates with Customers on a regular basis to provide requested services and provide assistance related to their account or order status. In these cases, we reply via e-mail or phone in accordance with the Customer's wishes.
Revision date- 7/1/2020.
Newsletter
Sign-up for monthly updates on new products, special promotions, and sales!
Newsletter
Monthly Sale!
For a limited time, save up to 20% off all 2021 CPT books. Offer ends 12/31/20.
Other limited time offers include:
Get 15% off 2021 coding bundles!
Get 10% off Optum360 ICD10 Experts!
Get 15% off 2021 CPT bundles!
Are you looking for a coupon code?
Connect with us on social media for weekly updates! Keep up with special offers, product releases, and more:
About Us
MedicalCodingBooks.com has been an authorized re-seller of code books, insurance forms, and software since 2003. Our most popular brands include ADA, AHA, AMA, Optum 360, and PMIC.
Additional coding information can be found on our medical resources page or company blog.
